&gt;&gt; Deep learning is a hands on empirical field.
&gt;&gt; ディープラーニングは 実践的な 実証研究分野です
The more experiments that we engineers and researchers try,
エンジニアや 研究者が 実験を 行えば 行うほど
the more ideas we generate and some of them actually turn out to work.
アイデアが たくさん生まれ その一部が 実際に 使えるものになります
Other ideas that seem promising initially don't work.
いけると 思ったアイデアでも うまく行かないものは あります
The practice is definitely ahead of the theory in many cases.
実践の方が 理論の先を 行くケースは 多くあります
And so it's important not to get too attached to theories about
ですから 各種ネットワークアーキテクチャーの 理論や
different network architectures or exactly what layer follows another in a network,
ネットワーク内の 層の順序などに 執着しすぎず
instead to be a successful deep learning practitioner,
ディープラーニングの 優れた実践者に なり
You need a bias towards action.
行動を 優先することが 大切です
Experiment to answer your questions rather than just thinking deep thoughts.
問いへの 答えは 深い思考ではなく 実験から 得るようにしましょう
Also don't be too discouraged if something
また 1回目の実験で すぐには うまく行かなくても
doesn't work immediately the first time you try it.
がっかりしないでください
Keep experimenting until you find
問題を解決する ネットワークと
a network and hyperparameters that work for your problem.
ハイパーパラメーターが 見つかるまで 実験を続けましょう
&gt;&gt; I like to think of deep learning as one of the few places in
&gt;&gt; ディープラーニングというのは コンピューターサイエンスの中で
computer science where we actually do science.
実際に 科学研究を行う 数少ない場の 1つだと思います
Most of computer science is really more about engineering,
コンピューターサイエンスの ほとんどは エンジニアリングですが
but in deep learning we really do spend a lot of time
ディープラーニングでは 多くの時間を費やして 実験を
running experiments and building theories of what works and why,
繰り返し 結果と原因から 理論を構築します
just like real scientists.
科学者らしい 作業ですよね
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I would say that does make us real scientists.
&gt;&gt; ええ 確かに 私たちの仕事は 科学者っぽいですね
You're learning about several important network architectures
これから プロジェクトの土台として使える
that you can use as a basis for your own projects.
重要な ネットワークアーキテクチャーについて 学びます
But more important than the intricacies of these networks,
しかし これらのネットワークの 詳細より大事なのは
is to get your hands dirty and try to solve real problems.
手を汚して 現場の問題に 挑むことです
This will develop your confidence and give you practical skills.
そうすれば 実践能力を 磨き 自信を つけることができます
&gt;&gt; With that in mind, let's look at that other networks from 2014,
&gt;&gt; それを 念頭に置き 2014年の 他のネットワークを 見てみましょう
which has its own strengths.
それぞれに 長所があります